DELIVERANCE TIME
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Hey, who dares me?!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Don't touch me!
You don't know me!
Yes!
And when I saw you...
Things you have never seen...
Yeah.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Let me go.
I wanna move now.
I wanna go.
Yeah.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the name of Jesus Christ, come back!
Right now!
Come back!
One, two, three!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Come back here!
Look here!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
It's a snake, python!
Watch the screen.
Who are you?!
I am his boss.
His boss?
Yeah.
Whose boss?
I am the boss of the boss.
The boss of the boss?
Yeah.
Where?
In his life.
OK, how many powers do you have?
Uncountless!
Uncountless?
Yeah.
What is your mission here?
To destroy.
To destroy?
What do you plan towards me?
It is secret; I don't want to tell you.
You don't want to tell me?
Never!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Watch your screen.
The brother is...
Remove this staff...
I don't wanna anyone to bother me.
I want to do my job now.
You want to do your job?
Yeah.
What is your job?
I don't wanna tell you.
Stand up!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Raise it up!
Up up up...!
Jump, jump, jump...!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Watch your screen.
I wanna go now.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
This guy is very dangerous.
He is a king of wizards.
Out of 186 powers, 180 have gone out.
Only six remains.
Confess and get free right now!
OK?
I was sent to destroy.
You were sent?
Yeah.
Who sent you?
The big boss.
Out!
Watch your screen.
Something...
Deliverance Time
He has turned into a tiger.
For you to know that there are many animals that live inside of him.
Deliverance Time
Watch your screen.
In the time of His earthly ministry, our Lord Jesus Christ had power over every evil spirit that killed.
Father, we thank You.
The one inside of him has gone but he has to confess everything.
DEMON-POSSESSED Man With 186 Evil Spirits DELIVERED!!!
Thank You, Jesus!
I am free!
Glory be to God!
There is a brother who came all the way from Mozambique.
TESTIMONY TIME
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Agostinho Jefue.
I am from Mozambique.
I am 43 years old.
I was born into witchcraft family that always used to worship and do ceremonies for the dead spirits.
That was how I was initiated with witchcraft spirits.
I had one hundred and eighty-six powers.
Every day, I used to manifest.
We used to go to graveyards for ceremonies and to make sacrifices for the dead people.
Because of that I was initiated and my life was upside down.
I remember that I went to a witch doctor looking for a solution and
he said to me that I had a prince of witchcraft spirit, which I had to take care of.
Otherwise, I could not get free.
He told me that the evil spirits inside of me loved me a lot.
I suffered and I lost everything.
I went to many places looking for deliverance.
They called me Cobra.
They told me to call all the demons in that area.
I called them and they came inside my body.
I became more aggressive than before.
But in that place, no one could help me.
I sold my things to get money to make sacrifices but that didn't help me.
Because I was offering a lot, I was told that there was someone else who could deliver me.
They took me there.
When I got there, the man said to me that I had a very old demon in my body which couldn't go out easily.
The man there said that I had to fast for twenty-one days without food or water.
I was on twenty-one days fasting.
Here I was during the process of fasting.
After that nothing happened.
Snakes and python used to manifest within me.
When I was in Mozambique I was hopeless.
I didn't know what to do.
I went to many places, looking for deliverance.
While I was watching TV, I found Emmanuel TV.
When I saw Emmanuel TV, I saw miracles; I saw many things happening.
So, I decided to come to Nigeria.
So, I came here.
DEMON-POSSESSED Man With 186 Evil Spirits DELIVERED!!!
Last week on Sunday, I saw the man of God for the first time.
When I was on the prayer line; even before the man of God came close to me, I had started to hate him -
the evil spirit inside of me.
I was trying to attack him because I didn't want to see him approaching me but the Holy Spirit
in the Prophet T.B. Joshua didn't allow it.
I just didn't have power to do that.
Man of God – Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me and delivered me.
Look here!
Deliverance Time
Since Sunday, I am delivered, I am free!
I didn't think that I could be free without paying money.
I was taught that only money could solve everything but God loves me so much and He delivered me, freely.
I didn't pay anything.
I came here and I am free now - I thank God for it.
DEMON-POSSESSED Man With 186 Evil Spirits DELIVERED!!!
What advice do you want to give to the viewers, and people that are listening?
My advice to viewers, please don’t get involved with witchcraft.
They deceive, they lie.
They can never help.
Only God is our solution.
You were trying to attack me physically.
Yes, I remember.
Something came to my mind to finish the man of God.
To...?
To finish the man of God.
To destroy the man of God.
So, something said that you should finish me?
Yes.
Wow.
The Holy Spirit didn't allow that.
We listened to some strange sounds, like...
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
What are the meanings?
It were the same sounds that I used to make while I was in Mozambique, when they asked me to go and call
all the evil spirits.
OK.
Let's assume I am not what I say I am - what would have happened?
If God were not in you and you were not a man of God, many bad things would be happening.
DEMON-POSSESSED Man With 186 Evil Spirits DELIVERED!!!
Glory be to God!
Mr. Agostinho Jefue has come to realise that serving the Lord is the only way to peace and comfort,
whereas serving satan is a sure way to bitterness, pain and death.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church Of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV – changing lives, changing nations and changing the world.